Guide to the Denise Levertov Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4. Correspondence
  - a. Incoming
    - Moseley, Jim, 1987, TMS (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Moseman, Carol R., 1997, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Moser, Barry, C. 1973 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Moser, Norman, 1968 - 1981 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Moses, D. - Moses, R., C. 1967 - C. 1982, TMS (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Mosher, Harriet, 1994, (Maine writers & publishers alliance), 1 TLS (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Mosher, Tom, 1985 - 1988 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Moss - Motchal, C. 1967 - C. 1986 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Motchan, Joseph, 1971, (Motchan's Design House) (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Motel 6, 1991, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Mott, Michael, 1995, 1ALS (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Mott - Mottr, 1970 - 1972 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Mottram, Eric, 1986, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Moyano, Maricla, 1959 - 1981, TMS (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Moyer, Jennifer, 1989 - 1994, (Moyer Bell), 3ALS (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Moyer - Moyo, C. 1964 - C. 1988 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Much - Mueller, C., 1975 - 1985 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Mueller, Lisel, 1969 - 1981 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Mueller, Ottilia, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Muffins, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 32)
    - Muckang, John, 1984 - 1987 (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Mulford, Patti, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Mullen, Kay, 1997, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Muller, Anna, N.D., 2ALS (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Muller, Gretchen, 1990, 3TLS (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Muller, Marlene, 1993, 3ALS (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - Muller, Peter, N.D., 1ALS (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Muller, Sally, 1995, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Mulliken, Louise, 1974 - 1981 (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Mullins, Brighde, 1993, 1TLs (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Mullins, James, 22 Sep. 1976 - 9 Aug. 1987 (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Mumford, E. - Mumford, L.., 1965 - 1984, TMS (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Mumford, Sophia, 1975 - 1981 (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Mumford, Sophia, 1989 - 1992, 5ALS (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Mund - Murphy, James, 1962 - 1989, TMS (Box 76, Folder 47)
    - Murphy, Joyce, 1951 - 1971 (Box 76, Folder 48)
    - Murphy, Joyce, 1972 - 1982 (Box 76, Folder 49)
    - Murphy, Julian - Musgraves, N.D. (Box 76, Folder 50)
    - Muske, Carol, 1995, 2TLS (Box 76, Folder 51)
    - Muste - Myers, J., N.D. (Box 76, Folder 52)
    - Myers, Neil, 1995, 3TMS (Box 76, Folder 53)
    - Myers, Russell, N.D., 1968, TMS, AMS (Box 76, Folder 54)
    - Myhr, Elizabeth, 1996, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 55)
    - Nac - Nag, C. 1977 - C. 1984, 1TLS (Box 76, Folder 56)
    - Nameroff, Rochelle, 1969, 1973, TMS (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Nomias, June, 1973 - 1982 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Naqvi, Nauman, 1996, 1TLS (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Nasm, Liz, N.D., 1ALS (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Nas - Nath, 1968 - 1974 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - National Writers' Union, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Natu - Nav, 1964 - 1973 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Naylor, Carolyn Taylor, 1977 - 1980, TMS (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Naylor, Keith, 1977, TMS (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Neal - Neild, C. 1971 - C. 1981, TMS (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Neelon, Ann and Richard [also Ann Parker - Neelon] [1 of 2], 1990 - 1993, 5ALS, 2TLS (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Neelon, Ann and Richard [also Ann Parker - Neelon] [2 of 2], 1994 - 1997, 9ALS, 2TLS (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Nejgebauer, Sasha, and Iver Gordana, 1970 - 1973 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Nelson, Howard, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Nelson, Jeremy, C. 1965 - 4 Dec. 1985, TMs (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Nelson, Liz, N.D., 1TLS (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Nelson, Lonnie, 1995 Mar. 8, 1TLS (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Nelson, Marjorie [Rachel Da Silva], 1993 Sept. 28, 1 T invitation (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Nelson, R. - Nelson, V., N.D., 1969 - 197? (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Nemerov, Howard, 1963 - 1967 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Neuman, Stephen, 1995 - 1996, 2TLS, 1ALS (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - New Directions, 1994, 3ALS (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - New Directions, 1971 Nov. 11, 1 TLS (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Newgarden, Albert, 27 May 1996, 1 ALS (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Newman, Marilyn, 1971 - 1972 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Newman, Joan, N.D., 1ALS (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - News - Newman, G., 1965 Dec. 1 - 1988 Mar. 30 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - News - Newton, M., 22 Jun. 1961 - 27 Jul. 1978 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Newth, Rebecca, Dec. 3 1975, 1ALS, 1TLS, 1PC (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Newton, Race, C. 1962 - C. 1975 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Newton, Race, C. 1976 - C. 1986 (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Newton, Race, 1989 - 1997, 18ALS (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Newton, Ray [Poetry review], N.D. (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - The New Yorker (Owen Ketherry), 9 Nov. 1992, 1TLS (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - New York Quarterly [William Packard], 1986 - 1987, 6TLS (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Nguyen Van Bong, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Nicholas - Nichols, Bill, C. 1983 - C. 1984 (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Nichols, Bob, N.D., 1TLS, 1ALS (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Nichols, Robert, C. 1919 - C. 1960, TMs (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Nichols, Robert, 1959 - 1962, TMs (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Nichols, Robert, 1963 - 1964, TMs (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Nichols, Robert, 1965 - 1966 (Box 77, Folder 42)
    - Nichols, Robert, 1976 - 1980, TMs (Box 77, Folder 43)
    - Nicholson - Nicol, C. 1962 - C. 1986 (Box 77, Folder 44)
    - Niebauer, Abigail, N.D., 1976 - 1980, TMs (Box 77, Folder 45)
    - Niebauer, Abigail, C. 1980, TMs (Box 77, Folder 46)
    - Niebauer, Abigail, 1981 - 1982, TMs, AMs (Box 77, Folder 47)
    - Niebauer, Abigail and Jimmy, 1983 - 1986 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Nied - Niv, 31 Mar. 1963 - 10 Sep. 1986 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Nilson, Rev. Jon, 28 Oct. 1997, 1ALS (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - 92nd Street Y: The Poetry Center, 1991 May 15, 1TLS (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Nobel, Jeremy, 29 Mar. 1978 - 1 Aug. 1986, TMs (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Nobel, Jeremy J, 1991 May 13, 1ALS, 1 TMs (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Noel, Bernard, 1985 Jan. 11 - 1987 Dec. 27 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Noel, Bernard [Includes 2TLS from Peggy L. Fox and 1ALS from James Laughlin], 1987 - 1994, 5ALS, 1TLS (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Noel House, Seattle, 1997, N.D., 1TLS, 2ALS (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Noel, Melanie, 1996 July 18, 1TLS (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Nojima Louis, Nikki, 1997, N.D., 1TLS, 2ALS, TMs, 17pp. (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Noll, Bink, 1966, Offprint (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Nooteboom, Dr. Bart, July 24, 1983, 1TLS, 1TMs (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Nor. - Nov., C. 1962 - C. 4 Oct. 1987, TMs (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Norber Konig, Sister Mary, Nov. 17 1967, TLS (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Norbutt, John, Jan. 16 1979, TLS (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Norman, Howard, 1983, 2TLS (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Normand, Beryl, Feb. 25, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Norris, Kathleen, C. 1971 - C. 1987, CF. Betty Kray, 2TLS, 1PC (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Norris, Kathleen, 1990 - 1996, 7TLS, 5ALS, 1TMs, 19 pp. (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - North, Cheryl, Sep. 27, 1972, TLS (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Bruce - Novoa [Dept. of Spanish & Portuguese, Yale University], 1974 - 1975, 1TLS, 2TNS (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Nurske, Dennis, N.D., 1ALS (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Nussen, June, C. 1957 - C. 1959 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Nye, Naomi Shihab, 1991, 1993, 2ALS (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Nyman, Leslie, C. 1973 - C. 1976 (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Oa - Ogd, n.d., 1968 - 1986, MSS (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1982 July - 1986 Sept., 2PC (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - O'Gorman, Ned [Jubilee], 1961 - 1979 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - O'Brien, Patrick, 1994, N.D., 5TLS, 1PC (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Ocso, Sr. Beverly, 1997, 1ALS (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - O'Daly, Bill and Kris, 1991 - 1996, 2ALS, 2TLS, 1 Invitation (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - O'Dell, E.K. [Angele Kapetanak], c. 1968 - 1975, 2TLS, 1ANS (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - O'Donohue, John, 1995, N.D., 3ALS (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Offen, Ron, 1991, 1996, 2PC (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Ogden, Don, 1980 - 1983, 2ALS, 2MNS (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Ohan - O'Hara, 1973 - 1986 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Ohannessian, Griselda [New Directions Publishing Co.], 1990 - 1996, 3 TLS, 3 AN, 1 PC (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - Old - Oli, 1970 - 1982 (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - O'Leary, Kevin, 1968 - 1985, AMs (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Ollier, Jacqueline [Université de Nice], 1966 Sept. 26 - 1977 June 7, 4ALS (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Olpadwala, Porus, August 26 1996, 1 TLS (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Olsen, Renate, Jan. 2,1994, 1 ALS (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Olsen, Tillie, N.D. (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Olsen, Charles & Betty, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Olsen, T. - O'N, C. 1972 - C. 1978 (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - O'Neill, Kit, 1995, 1996, 1TLS, 1ALS (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Onofri, Francesca, June 15, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - Oppen, George, N.D., 1962 - 1980 (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - Oppen, George, N.D., 3TLS (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Oppenh - Ort, 1963 - 1983, TMs (Box 78, Folder 51)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel: Correspondence regarding the War Resisters League Calendar, 1968, C. 1967 - C. 1983, 2TLS, 1TMS (Box 78, Folder 52)
    - Orvino, Jennie, 1968 - 1973, TMs (Box 78, Folder 53)
    - Osborne, Charles, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 54)
    - Osborne, W. - Ossman, Dave, N.D. (Box 78, Folder 55)
    - Osborne, Ken, 1970 - 1976, TMs (Box 78, Folder 56)
    - Osterlund, Steve: Broadside, 1966 - 1982 (Box 78, Folder 57)
    - Osti - Ostr, 1975 - 1984 (Box 78, Folder 58)
    - Ottavelli, Charlotte [Washington State Secretary of State], Oct. 17 1996, 1TLS (Box 78, Folder 59)
    - Ourin, Victor, N.D., TMs (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Ourin, Victor: Photograph, N.D. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Ourin, Victor: Printed Material, C. 1969 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Ourin, Victor: Published work, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Ourin, Victor, 1972, 1977, TMs (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Overstreet, Roy H., 1994, 2TLS (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Owen - Owens, C. 1947 - C. 1988, TMs (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Owens, Virginia Stem [The Milton Center; Kansas Newman Center], Nov. 25 1996, 1TLS (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Oxenhandler, Noelle, N.D. (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - P Miscellaneous, May 27 1969 - Mar. 31 1980 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Pace, Barney, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Pacernick, Gary, 1996 - 1997, 3 TLS, 3 ALS, 3 PC (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Pack, Bernard, June 27, 1994, 1 TLS (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Pack, Robert, 1961 - 1962 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Packard, William, N.D., 1984 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Packer, Nancy, July 23, 1992, 1 TLS (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Packer, Nancy, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Page, Ethel, C. 1963 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Page, William, 1973 - 1974, TMs (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Page, William, 1975 - 1981, TMs (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Paley, Grace, 1975, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Paley, N - Palmer, D., c. 1968 - 1988 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Paley, Steve & Laurie, N.D., 1 PC (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Palmer, Gayle, Sep. 11, 1996, 1 TLS (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Palmer, George A., 1962 - 1966, TMs (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Palmer, George A. [Phoebe Palmer], 1962, TMs (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Palmer, George, C. 1967 - C. 1970, TMs (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Palmer, George, 1971 - 1976 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Palmer, Miriam [Miriam Dyak], 1970 - 1975, TMs (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Palmer, Phoebe [George Anthony Palmer], c. 1968 - 1972 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Palmer, Phoebe, 1973 - 1976 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Palmer, Phoebe, 1977 - 1985 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Palmer, Sarah, c. 1977 - c. 1979 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Palmer, Tom, c. 1970, TMs (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Pan - Parkh, 1971 - 1988, TMs (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Paola, Suzanne, Sep. 24 1996, 1TLS; 1 TLS from Marlene Muller, secretary, to Suzanne Paola (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Papadopoulos, Nov. 26 1995, 1ALS (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Papadopoulos, Katerina, N.D., 1TLS (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Parkinson, Thomas, c. 1958 - c. Jan. 18 1972 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Parl - Parse, c. 1968 - c. 1981 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Parsons, Kitty, 1977 - 1980 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Parsons, Richard, 1981 - 1982 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Part - Pat, N.D., c. 1970 - c. 1982 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Pascal, Naomi [ Univ. of Washington Press], August 2, 1995, 1TLS (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Pasternak, Boris, Feb. 1960, ALS, [Facism] (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Pasternak, Boris, Feb. 7 1960, ALS (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Pattee, Patti [Watermark Book Co.], 1993, PC (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Paul, James, 1982 - 1988, TMs (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Paulsen, Faith, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Pawlak, Mark [1of 2], c. 1971, TMs (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Pawlak, Mark [2 of 2], c. 1971, TMs (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Pawlak, Mark, N.D., c. 1964 - c. 1979, TMs (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Pawlak, Mark, 1978 - 1987, TMs (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Pawlak, Mark, 1991 - 1993, 3ALS, 3TLS (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Payne, Robert, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Payne, Stephen R., 1978, TMs (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Paz, Octavio, 1958 - 1966, TMs (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Pea - Pearl, 1975 - 1979, TMs (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Peacock, Molly, July 29, 1991, ALS (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Peacock, Nancy, 1996 - 1997, ALS, 4PC (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Pearl, Nancy, May 23, 1996, 2TLS (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Pearson, Norman, c. 1959 - c. 1975 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Pearson, S. - Peb, c. 1977 - c. 1988 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Pease, Roland [Zoland Press], 1991 - 1997, 2TLS, 7ALS, 1PC (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Peck, Louise & Sid, Dec. 16, 1989, 1PC (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Peck, Sidney, c. 1974 - c. 1985 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Pecorelli, Ruth, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Pedote, Sharon, Oct. 8, 1991, TLS (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Peet, Graham - Peet, Olivia, 1975 - 1984 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Peet, Stephen [& Olivia], 1988 - 1997, 13ALS, 3PC (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Peet, Stephen, N.D., 1948 - 1952 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1956 - 1961 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1974 - 1975 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1974, TMs (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1974, TMs (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1962 - 1973 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Peet, Stephen, c. 1978, TMs (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1976 - 1978 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1979 - 1980 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1981 - 1984 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Peet, Stephen, 1985 - 1988 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Peet, Suzi [Daughter of Stephen Peet], 1979 - 1986 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Pegnalli, Peter, Mar. 20, 1990, TLS, ALS (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Pei - Pel, 1972 - 1987, TMs (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Pelka, Fred, Sep. 12, 1990, TLS (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Pena, Jerry, 1977, AMs (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Penn - Perp, c. 1964 - c. 1988, TMs (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Perl, Jeffrey, Sep. 15, 1991, ALS (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Perrault, Bernadette, 1986 -1988, ALS (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Perry: - Perry, N.D., 1980 - 1983 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Persell, Nancy, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Persk - Pes, 1968 - 1977 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Peter, Melanie, N.D. (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Peter, Melanie: Letters, manuscripts, & articles, N.D. (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Peter, Melanie, 1986 - 1988 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Peter, Melanie, N.D., 2ANS, 2ALS (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Peter, Melanie: Article about Annie Dillard, N.D. (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Petermann, W., c. 1984 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Petr - Pett, 1962 - 1978, TMs (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Peters, D. - Peters, Rachel, c. 1971 - c. 1985, TMs (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Peters, Robert, 1966 - 1975, TMs (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Peterson, K - Peterson, M., 1968 - 1986 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Peterson, Brenda, May 10, 1995, TLS (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Peterson, Paulann, 1997, ALS (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Peterson, Paulann, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Peterson, Robert, 1959 - 1961 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Pfei - Pfeufer, J., 1967 - 1969 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Pfeufer, Robbie & Leven, 1973 - 1986 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Phelps, Lyon, 1980, TMs (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Phelps, Richard, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Phillips, Glen. "Time Capsule", c. 1979, TMs (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Phillips, J. - Phosy, 1964 - 1983 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Phillips, Robert [Bob], 1962 - July 18, 1995, 7TLS, TMs (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Philyp, Patricia, N.D., ALS, PC (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Phillips, William [Partisan Review], 1968 - 1972, 2 TLS (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Piatt, Harry, 1964 - 1965 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Pic - Pierce, 1962 - 1985 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Pierce, Gay, 1992, 2 TLS (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Piercy, Marge, Nov. 22, 1972 - Augusr 5, 1987, TMs (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Pigors, Sylvia, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Pillin, William, 1958 - 1962, TMs (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Pitofsky, Robert, Sep. 1992, ALS, TLS (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Pitofsky, Sally, N.D., ALS, ANS (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Pin - Piz, N.D., 1964 - 1984 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Pineda, Marianna, 1993 - 1994, 2 ALS (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Pistone, Bob, July 1992, 3 ALS (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Pitchford, Kenneth [War Resisters League Calendar, 1968], 1967, TLS (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Pla - Plo, c. 1963 - c. 1983 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Plagentine, B., Dec. 20 1956, ALS (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Plante, Paul [Gallery Invitation], Nov. 5, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Plumridge, Jerri [Seed], July 25, 1997, TLS (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Pocock, Gerry, 1977 - 1988, TMS (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Pocock, Gerry [ 1of 2], 1989 - 1992, 11 ALS, 6 TLS (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Pocock, Gerry [ 2of 2], 1993 - 1997, 3 ALS, 4 TLS, 3 PC (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Pointer, Jonathon & Madeleine Smithberg, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Poirotte, Louis, 1951 - 1958 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Pol - Pollard, A., 1964 - 1985 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Polite, Frank, Feb. 3, 1964, ALS (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Politkoff, [?] Joan, July 1996, ALS (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Pollard, Barbara [Beatrice Levertoff Foundation], 1976 - 1988 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Pollard, R. - Por., 1973 - 1985 (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Popko, John, July 21, 1995, TLS (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Porter, Arabel [Houghton Mifflin], 1970 - 1977 (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Porter, Christy, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - Porter, Norman, 1963 - 1965 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - Porter, Rosemary, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - Porter, Doraine, 1979 - 1980, TMs (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Posner, David, N.D., TMs (Box 82, Folder 38)
    - Posner, David, N.D., 1962 - 1963 (Box 82, Folder 39)
    - Posner, David, 1963 - 1965, TMs (Box 82, Folder 40)
    - Posner, David, 1964 - 1966 (Box 82, Folder 41)
    - Posner, David, 1967 - 1968, TMs (Box 82, Folder 42)
    - Posner, David, 1970 - 1973, TMs (Box 82, Folder 43)
    - Posner, David, 1974, TMs (Box 82, Folder 44)
    - Posner, David, 1974 - 1976 (Box 82, Folder 45)
    - Posner, David, 1977- 1980 (Box 82, Folder 46)
    - Posner, David, 1982 - 1983 (Box 82, Folder 47)
    - Posner, Dominic; Olivia Posner [cross reference David Posner], 1980; 1985 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Posner, E. - Posner, R., 1976 - 1981 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Postel, Barbara [also Barbara Hammond; Barbara Cherish], c. 1965 - c. 1978 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Postel, Louis, c. 1947 - c. 1974, TMs (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Postel, Louis, 1966, TMs (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Postel, Louis. "The Next In Line", c. 1966 - c. 1968, TMs (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Poston, Jane, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1989 - 1993, 12 ALS, 1 ANS (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Potter, Carolyn, 1989- 1997, 2 ANS, 15 ALS (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1919 - 1952 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1953 - 1957 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1958 - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1964 - 1969 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1970 - 1972 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1973 - 1977 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1978 - 1979 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Potter, Caroline, 1980 - 1985 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Potter, Nancy, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Potter, Nic, Dec. 29, 1995 - June 23, 1996, 2 ALS (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Potter, Norman, 1959, TMs (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Poulin, Al, 1990, 2 ANS, 3 TLS (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Poulin, Al Jr. [Boa Editions Limited], 1994 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Poulin, Albert, 1967 -1975 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Poulin, Albert, 1976 -1988 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Pow - Poy, 1972 -1980 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Powell, Mel, 1991 May 15, 1 TLS (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Praloran, Sabrina, 1993, 2 ALS (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Pratt, Steve Paul, 1991, ALS, 1 chapbook (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Presler, Sue W., Feb. 6, 1995, TLS (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Preston, Jane [Poets House], July 17, 1991, TLS (Box 83, Folder 30)
    - Primosh, James, 1994 - 1997, 4 TLS, 1 TMs (Box 83, Folder 31)
    - Pre - Pritchard, J., 1959 - 1983, TMs (Box 83, Folder 32)
    - Pritchard, Sheila, 1956 - 1964 (Box 83, Folder 33)
    - Pritchard, Sheila, 1965 - 1968 (Box 83, Folder 34)
    - Pritchard, Sheila, 1969 - 1975 (Box 83, Folder 35)
    - Pritchard, Sheila, 1976 - 1987 (Box 83, Folder 36)
    - Pro - Pul, 1973 - 1987, AMs, TMs (Box 83, Folder 37)
    - Puffer, Linda, 1991, ALS (Box 83, Folder 38)
    - Qa - Quai, c. 1968 - c. 1982, AMs (Box 83, Folder 39)
    - Quartermain, Peter, OCT. 14 1996, TLS (Box 83, Folder 40)
    - Quasha, George, 1968 Jan. 13, TMs (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Quasha, George, 1968 July, TMs (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Quasha, George, 1968 Aug. - Sept. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Quasha, George, 1968 Oct. - Dec. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Quasha, George, Jan. 6, 1969 - Mar. 14, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Quasha, George, April 27, 1969 - April 28, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Quenon, Brother Paul [ Merton Foundation], June 6, 1997, 1 TLS, 3 TM (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Quigley, Kate, August 7, 1991, ALS (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Quinn, Alice, Oct. 5, 1991 - Oct. 21, 1991, 2 TNS (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Quinn, Sister Bernetta, April 23, 1997, ALS (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Quinn, Sister Bernetta, 1968 - 1969 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Quinn, Sister Bernetta, 1970 - 1971 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Quinn, Sister Bernetta, 1973 - 1975 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Quinn, Patricia, 1984 - 1986 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Quinter, David, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Misc. R, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Raban, Jonathon, April 9, 1991, TLS (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Rabin, Jules, Jan. 22, 1997, TLS (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Ragdale Foundation [Alice Hayes], Jan. 1989, TLS (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Radack, Eric, c. 1977 - c. 1989 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Radil, G., c. 1976 - c. 1982 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Radin, Doris, 1964 - 1986, TMs (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Raffel, Burton, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Rago, Henry [Poetry Magazine], c. 1959 - c. 1974 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Ragsdale, "Rags", 1991 - 1993, 1 ALS, 5 TLS, 1 TNS (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Rainbow, Dee Dee, 1996 - 1997, ANS, ALS (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Rah - Raim, 1958 - 1987 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Rainer, Dachine, 1961, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Raines, Cindy and Bob [Kirkridge], 1986 - 1989 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1994 - 1995, 3 ALS, 1 TM (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1995 - 1997, 5 ALS, 3 TLS, 4 TM (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1973 - 1974 (Box 84, Folder 32)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1975 - 1978 (Box 84, Folder 33)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1979 - 1980 (Box 84, Folder 34)
    - Rainey, Carol. "Passengers", 1981, TMs (Box 84, Folder 35)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1981 - 1982 (Box 84, Folder 36)
    - Rainey, Carol, 1982, TMs (Box 84, Folder 37)
    - Rainey, Carol. "From The Journals, 1972 - 1982", 1982, TMs (Box 84, Folder 38)